

contact@johnevanofski.net

720 938 4999

Oakland, Bay Area CA http://johnevanofski.net

BIO

John Evanofski is a Bay Area web developer and designer with a diverse technological skillset and a problem solving aptitude. He is also an adept verbal and written communicator and an experienced technology educator. Please enjoy responsibly!

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer and Creative Technologist Teak / San Francisco CA / 2014-Now

Freelance Web Developer
David Kerr Design / Oakland CA / 2012-2014

Web and Graphic Design Lead Clean LED Energy / Oakland CA / 2014

Web Developer and Tech Support YogaKula / Berkeley CA / 2012-2014

Freelance Web and Graphic Design Cindy Cleary Art / 2014 Mission Creek Festival / Oakland CA / 2013

Teaching

HTML & CSS, Computing / Tutor / Wyzant.com / 2014 WordPress / AcademyX / 2013 Excel '98 & 2010 / ServiceSource Inc / 2009-2013

SKILLS

WEB

- HTML5 & CSS3
- Responsive Web
- WordPress CMS
- JavaScript
- Ruby
- PHP

ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- AfterEffects

OTHER

- Final Cut Pro
- Microsoft Office Suite

EDUCATION

Liberal Arts Humanities (AA)
Digital Art Certificate
City College San Francisco / 2013

Web Design Certificate

AcademyX / 2011

